We're now
Come and play a game
OK
You're going to the green grassland
Find your brother
then
Put this Rubik's Cube
Leave it to him
Missions we cannot complete
I'll give it to you
Are you ready?
Although it is ready
But I didn't expect it to be so unreasonable
Not really
Better than my house
No one who can compare with you is an ordinary sheep
I did the trick too late last night
I don't know how to fall asleep
Today is the day when my dad and mom come back again
I just want to ask everyone to help me with it
You are welcome
We must be clean and clean!
Let’s start!
good
Completed!
Dad Mom
We'll be able to meet soon
Wait for me to put the book back to the cabinet
Just pick them up
Can't you land properly?
It's all in vain
Let's pick them up quickly!
dad
mother
you…
Who are you?
Catch you!
Pleasant goat
elder brother!
elder brother?
I'll eat frogs tonight
Where is the frog?
There!
Don't run!
Haven't eaten meat for a long time
Go home to add food
Brother Brother Brother
Little sister
I'm not your brother
Brother Brother!
I am my sister!
What a cute lamb!
What's your name?
My name is Bingbingyang!
Then what is your brother’s name?
Brother is called brother!
What is dad and mom's name
Dad called Dad
Mom calls mom
Since they are of the same race
We took back to Sheep Village
Ask whose child it is
Let's go and ask the village chief!
Where is the Bingbing Sheep?
There!
Find your brother! Find your brother!
Don't run away!
Bingbing Sheep
You wait for us...
God really helps me!
strangeness
Just now
I could hear the sound of Bingbing Sheep
Look there!
Don't want to be injured
Just help me unseal it...
Otherwise
Don't blame me for being rude...
stop
Big Big Wolf
Do you want to frick
Even the little girls want to bully
It's okay, Bingbing Sheep
It's OK…
It's very dangerous for a little girl to run around
Come on, let's go home first
Let's go home first!
No way to leave
Big Big Wolf
You can go
But this little thing is not allowed to leave
Big Big Wolf, what's wrong with you?
Stop being rude!
Let go quickly!
Pleasant Goat...
Is it okay? Pleasant goat?
What are you fricking, Big Big Wolf?
Come down with me quickly!
What happened to Big Big Wolf?
Next!
Bingbing Sheep
It's okay, Bingbing Sheep
Fun, fun
Big Big Wolf
How do you treat children like this!
You are a father!
What happened to you today
You're so upset
Strengthened modification
All will disappear to me
Pleasant Goat!
Big Big Wolf, you...
This weapon is so powerful!
Everyone, hurry away from Big Big Wolf!
He seems to be a little strange
Bingbing Sheep, you're fine
Gray...too...wolf
I'm Pleasant Goat
I…
We are good friends
This...this is
Affordable
It should be eliminated
Pleasant goat
There is no more slag left
It's a cheater
He's there
How did he hide from that gun
Go there
What's going on
Feeling unable to control
Your body's speed is
My shoes
Changed?
It's hard to tell...
Difficult to tell
He used the energy of the super cube
Then you disappear with the Rubik's Cube
My speed
Sure enough, it's getting faster
Oops Oops
What should I do if something has a ghost?
Me too…
Your attack
It's invalid for me
Decide to the beef, Big Grey
Here
Firepower is fully opened!
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
you…
Did I miss your brain?
You're just holding a super powerful weapon
Chasing us and fighting
You won't do anything
It's not happening
What nonsense
Why would I chase you and fight
I just want to catch a frog
I'm almost hungry
Not coming back yet
I'll come back soon
Come back soon
I'm going home to cook
Let's talk about it next time
Bingbing sheep!
Take her back to Yang Village for treatment!
Bingbingyang
There is no record of her in the clan
Then ~
Is it hard to be a child from other villages
It's possible
Now we can only
Take Bingbing Sheep in first
Until her parents are found
and…
This mysterious box...
I remember hitting it at that time
A sudden energy swelled into the body
But after the ability disappears
How to touch it
No response...
Dad told me
This is called the Super Power Cube!
It turned out to be Bingbing Sheep's father's thing
Leave it to me for research first
See if you can find any traces
Looking for Bingbing Sheep's parents
I'll give it to you
good!
Right
Pleasant Goat Your Dad Mother
Haven't come back yet
them
Should be busy
I haven't been back yet
Don't know Bingbing Sheep's father and mother
What are you doing now
Don't know the Pleasant Goat
Do you want to accept this sister or not
Hope he can accept it