Don't know Weslie
Hope he can accept it
But
Don't worry
Wait for him to another galaxy
We'll go back to see Weslie when we have time
The refrigeration progress should be almost the same
What is Dad looking at
Dad, mom, let's play hide-and-seek
You turn around quickly
Don't run around. Some places are very dangerous
The Bacteria King has entered dormant state
Let's go seal the hall
Um
Hiding here will definitely not find me
Let's start
I'll hand it over to you here
Open the container
Prepare to record the fingers
Close the container quickly!
Start closing
You come out soon! !
I didn't expect you to sleep
Is this cold and want to make me sleepy?
Too naive!
I've been waiting for you to come in!
what
BB Goat?
This
This...this...
Unlock to me
Dad, what is that?
So cute
No!
The sealed fingers of BB Goat were recorded
what
You come out first!
good
Where did you go
The Bacteria King escaped
It actually sealed my abilities
I will definitely not be good at slack off!
With good dad and mom
Where to go!
She must have sealed my power
Yes or no!
Hand over the little things and help me unseal them
I'll let you go! Hahaha
You take BB Goat to escape first
I'm going to get the super magic cube now
You're the only one
No time
Believe me
What do you want to do!
I'll tell you the old thing
Even if you have a super cube in this body, you won't be able to use it...
Even so, we have to hold him back!
Undoubted resistance!
Mom Where is Dad?
BB Goat, mother is going to find dad now
Then play games with BB Goat
You have to stay here, it's not a bad idea
Do you know?
Um
I won't run away
You need to come back soon
Um
Have to go back tight
Go quickly
Can't get rid of it!
careful!
Li goat! !
I'm fine
We were all trapped, it seems we can't escape.
BB Goat and Magic Cube
We're back
Dad, mom!
I heard it, let's play a new game now
BB Goat
You have to keep this cube
Go to Qingqing Grassland to hand it over to your brother
knew
Don't hide it!
The green grassland is the old town of my father and mother
Go home and find your brother
Your brother is called Weslie!
What goat?
We believe in you
BB Goat will ask you
He actually ran away!
Dad, mom, when will you come back...
Weslie Brother
When did you take me to find my brother?
I'm now
oops
The inventors of these two things are amazing
Village Chief, have you found any trace?
Um…
I can't understand this technology at all
no
The largest inventor on the grassland
I must break these two things!
You come and move it to me
You wait a moment
I'll look for you later.
Moving is finished!
Where is BB Goat?
I know my super smelly machine is hurt!
who!
careful!
ah
Freshing sauce
Fortunately, freshener was added...
Uncle, it’s you again!
Have we seen it?
Last time you chased me and played!
How is it possible
I've been catching frogs lately. When...
How are you here
Did you... I miss your brain?
I can't tell that I'm young
Something went wrong in my brain? !
Uncle, do you know where my brother is?
I can't find him
What is your brother’s name?
As long as you say it
I've been catching goat for many years
It will definitely help you find it!
Very good!
I don't know what my brother is
But I think he has two eyes
Have a mouth and two ears
Who is not like this
Is he my brother?
You're a goat
Is your brother definitely a monkey
Do you understand
Or I will take him back to Yang Village!
Little sister, you don't have any traces
It's very difficult to find your brother
Stop me!
Who are you
It's you again! Not a little bit!
You're the little one
I am the germ king that everyone is proud of
I'm the king
Your fake
How dare I be unfair to this king!
The only ability of this king after being sealed
Control the invasion!
Can invade some body dirty
Go in! Take control of them!
Control successfully!
Finally caught you
This guy named Wolffy is too dirty!
How long has it been since I took a shower?
This king loves clean bacteria!
If it weren't for the fact that I could only invade my body
I don't want to control this dirty body!
Wolffy?
There!
It's them again
Can't let them come
Controlled by this king
His ability to be strong can be enhanced by his original ability
Look at my super invention!
Wolffy is in trouble again!
So smelly! Be careful, everyone!
snort! There was no one falling down
Wolffy, please be awake!
Now let you accompany them
See how long you can last
I can't hold on anymore
Haha, no goat will stop me
I want to defeat the bad guys and protect my father and mother
If you have younger brothers and younger sisters in the future
Will you protect your dad and mom like
It will definitely be!
Don't try to escape
You'll wait for me
One day, this king will catch a small matter
Help me unblock!
By then it will be your end!
It turns out that he caught BB Goat to understand the sealing ability
What ability?
I don't know that I can't let him succeed in the end
Weslie Brother!
You're fine, are you injured?
It's okay, I'm not going to run away
You promised me not to go wrong
I'll help you find your brother
good!
Let's hook