New family
This invention is really amazing and you must be careful
Slow! Hahahahaha
BB Goat!
Come and chase me!
BB Goat! ! !
Slowy!
BB Goat Be good!
I don't want it
Slow hug hug
What's up?
BB Goat has only been playing for the past few days
I didn't sleep much
Children need to coax them when they sleep
Baby, beloved, go to bed quickly
Go to bed quickly. Baoba
Wow~! The village chief is so terrible!
…
Hahaha….
Alas ~
The village chief hasn't had a rest for a few days for the super cube
well…
Hey!
Why did you fall asleep too?
Then we want to do our best to coax BB Goat to sleep
Don't beat the village chief and have a rest
Um
yes!
Wipe the window too!
It's OK and it's OK
This familiar feeling...
How come it is more dirty than last time!
Why am I so cute
To get my strength back
I endured it! ! !
Just used this arm stick
My figure is going to be so good
Come and try
Don't hesitate
Let's try
I'm too weak and can't carry it...
Hehehe~ I'll catch you
Wolffy?
Where are you going?
Aren't you going to sweep Wolf Castle?
I am a king, you actually let me come and fight?
what?
You say it again
You let me come and swipe? No door!
I seem to be shaking
It seems that Wolffy is afraid of this female wolf!
Forget it... Forget it, I don't want to live in such a dirty place either
What to watch? Watch! Quickly swipe!
Yes Yes Yes Yes...
As long as she is tired of playing
She will naturally fall asleep
BB Goat, are we good to play games?
good!
Then you catch me
Brother, don't run away!
continue! Continue!
Click on my experience
As long as BB Goat is allowed to eat, you will naturally want to sleep
Where is BB Goat?
Brother Yangyang
Is there any more?
Is the rest good for me?
This method also failed
Still that spirit
Let me come and hug
Does BB Goat like to hear stories?
like!
From then on there was a big tree with sky...
BB Goat has begun to commit crimes
Later they...
This story is so boring!
I want to hear the Black Snow Prince
Has Wolffy finished sweeping?
Come and see how bad this king is
Let's take a look at the table that I wiped by
Very well done!
Hahaha, I love clean
You will be satisfied now!
That way I can...
Continue to swipe other places
Shred up clean points!
Is this king doing this?
After this king returns his abilities
Let me see how I deal with you! !
You call me?
not…! no! !
I'll go swipe
When is Wolf Castle so big?
At this speed now, I can't get my abilities back
There is a way! ah……!
nailed it
Let's start swiping
I'm going to catch BB Goat!
What happened to the swipe?
Wolffy!
I've handed over to you...
BB Goat, go to bed quickly
I don't want to sleep, I want to play, I don't want to
I want to play I want to play...!
Weslie We should sleep
No, I don’t sleep, I want to play!
Being slapped again, let me come
dad
You're going to stop sleeping
The snail is about to bite you
The snail is here
catch…
Catch the snail and get caught...
Got asleep
Finally fell asleep!
Hum!
Be calm!
Hahahahahahahahaha~
Um?
Go quickly Go quickly... Wolffy is controlled again!
Found it. Hand over BB Goat!
Hand over BB Goat!
Take care of BB Goat for me, I will wake up Wolffy!
Um!
BB Goat
You're going to run with BB Goat
We stop him!
whee! I want to hold this king
I won't play with you anymore
Wow!
Wake up quickly! Wolffy...
Hahaha, I am very sober!
Ah ~
BB Goat!
I will definitely protect you!
It's also a hindrance to me!
Soon... can't hold back
No...want...get...get...get
Come here for me! Come over here...uh! ?
What are you doing? Quick! Quick...!
I will definitely come back!
Huh? How could I say this...
It's nothing
Am I swiping?
Why did you suddenly lie outside?
Where is this?
Just now you were controlled by a guy who called himself the king!
Can't I really be controlled?
OK I haven't been hurt this time. Red, I'll reply...
So clean! But why don’t you see all the furniture?
Red Where are you
Where is it?
Red! You're fine
I'm fine
But
You'll have something to do soon!
What... What happened?
Let you clean your home
You really threw everything away!
Red! You hear me explain!
oops
This wolf is really hard to serve...
My favorite father, mother, brother
Weslie Brother...
I'll definitely find your family.