You can take these medicines on time
Thank you, doctor
Next
Doctor! Save me!
You're cold
You say
Doctor Do I have geriatric disease?
Clam? Dementia in the elderly?
That's right I've often forgotten what I've done recently
Red Good morning!
Wolffy!
What's up? Red
Look at the good things you did!
I haven't done it
Then why do these have your claw marks
Bad dad!
What happened to Wilie?
You steal my lollipop!
Then how could it happen? Dad doesn't like eating
Wolffy!
That's how the doctor
OK OK OK
You can calm down first, let me check it out
Nothing happened, it's just a bit of bacterial infection
Just give you some medicines to disinfect
Doctor, you're fine, right?
Nothing is OK
Come to you with medicine
Hahaha
Sorry, I have close eyes
Remember to use the medicine as timely
Thank you
Where is my eye lens?
Recently, it has appeared on the grassland
I call myself the germ king
There is a bad egg in the universe, which is also called this name
The bacterium king in the universe has great power
Destruction of all four parts, no evil
Whether it is the same person or not, everyone must be careful
His goal seems to be Bingbing Yang
Yes, he also said what energy he wanted to use her to unblock
Unsealing energy?
No matter what he wants to do
We must protect Bingbing Yang
yes!
Very good, but I need to find her brother
You decide whose home she lives in
I'll go back to study the Rubik's Cube first
Village chief walk slowly!
The kids are grown up and can handle everything
Bingbing Yang live in my house!
We can have a fight together!
Or come to my house. Sister and you are all kinds of flowers!
Come to my house, sister learn with you
Come to my house, I have a lot of snacks!
How do you choose her like this
That's what I said
I've thought of it
We can make her a secret base
Then you can move over and live with her together!
Yes! Then everyone can accompany Bingbing Yang together
This is a good idea
Secret base!
How to use this
The doctor must have given me a mistake
I'm really, just that bacterial infection is that simple?
There's a way again
Stealing lollipops done
Destroyed Wolf Castle completed
I will put the matter of Bingbing Yang aside
It's not bad to go eat, drink and have fun
Isn't this the dirty and grey taro?
Just in time to go play again
Completed!
Go to play!
Completed
Let me let me go
The secret base should be equipped with more fitness equipment to be healthy!
Add more plants to freshen!
Put more snacks and drink!
Spread more books and gain knowledge!
Let me go, let me go, let me go
ah……
You're fine, right?
Fun!
I still want to play!
You still want to play...
But that's too dangerous
Have it!
With this slide, you are not afraid of danger
Brother Weslie, you are so nice to me!
thank you!
Help! ! ! …
What's up? Come and play with me!
So delicious!
Don't run away!
Where is this?
Just now you were controlled by a germ called the king
It turns out... it turns out that someone is really controlling me!
Oops exposed!
I want to catch you back
Finally got off work
Invasion mode!
Let's see who caught!
The mission is done!
Bingbing Yang can live here in the future
Do you like it?
Help!
It's the germ king!
Let's deal with him together!
Weslie and the others are really reliable!
Tell me your purpose!
Why didn't I control Wolffy this time
Bingbing Yang is here too, then hand her over!
You'll take Bingbing Yang first
I'll hold him back!
Want to escape
Not that easy
Ah, not good!
Secret base! Everyone, please leave here!
ah!
Wolffy!
Hold on!
stop!
Stop me!
careful
Doctor
I'm here!
oh! Sorry, I have close eyes
Right! Weslie
Go and take his eyeglasses off
what
Wild pig doctor
It's a close eye
I see!
Catch Wolffy!
You wait for me!
Don't want to run
Wolffy!
Weslie!
We're here to help!
Where is the Bacteria King?
It's nothing left, he's been taken away by us
Let's go and save Mr. Wild Pig
Um
The secret base we have worked hard to build has collapsed...
It seems that Bingbing Yang can only live in my house
I want to live in Brother Weslie!
Can't live with Sister Tibbie?
Let's have flowers together
not good! I'm going to live with Brother Weslie!
Hahahahahaha...
Why does Bingbing Yang just want to live with Weslie?
Because you only consider yourself
Village Chief!
Although you built a secret base for Bingbing Yang
Just show what you like
You just think about what you like
Only Weslie is thinking about what Bingbing Yang needs
Of course she likes Weslie
Sorry Bingbing Yang
We only care about ourselves
I never asked what you like
Please tell us
Brothers and sisters, let’s go back to Yang Village!
You're going to teach me what to do
Um!
Then who will return to Goat Village as soon as possible!
good!
He actually ran away
This... what's going on!
It's hard to tell
It's impossible!
I'm no longer under control!
It turns out you are here!
Red, you hear me explain
This time I really didn’t do the red red red red red!
How dare you knock over my makeup? I have nothing to do with you!
It turns out that I didn't do
I thought I was controlled again
Wolffy Come and help!
Yes red!