The weather is so hot
So thirsty! I really want to drink water!
Village Chief, I'll help you
Village Chief
The water you want
Village Chief, take a break
Thank you for your Pleasant Goat
The battle to get started
It's so terrible
Don't cry Don't cry I'll come to help you
Your wind
Who is here to help me
Such a big wooden barrel
Wrapped in my body...
Thank you Pleasant Goat
Come
What a great thing. Pleasant Goat can help so many people
If only I had the equipment as well
Installation
Finally packed
Big Big Wolf must have never thought of it
I actually live on the ceiling of their house
In this clean environment
I'll definitely come up with a way to catch the Bingbing Sheep
It still makes people think about things! !
Let me see what Big Big Wolf is trying to frick
Why is this refrigerator so complicated
Even I can’t handle it even if I’m an inventor!
Even if you don't have any repairs in the refrigerator, you're so embarrassed to call yourself an inventor
Try this
The clumsy man still wants this king to take action
Is it troublesome to repair a refrigerator?
Just use this one
Fixed
But the refrigerator has a poor refrigeration capability
I didn't have any ice cream I put last time
change!
Finish!
But the chocolate I put last time was only eaten for two days
Increase the capacity too!
Now it's all done
I'll check the results!
It's changed a little bit
etc! Or maybe you can use it to catch the Bingbing Sheep!
No one is here...
As long as I get the energy cube
Maybe it can be as darn like Pleasant Goat!
What are you fricking here?
Alas... Village chief...
Oops, was it discovered?!
I...I'm afraid that the energy cube will be stolen by a bad person
I have the super anti-blocking system I invented
Who can't take the Rubik's Cube under my nose!
Almost contacted the alarm...
OK I'm going out to retrieve materials
Has been taken away! !
Village Chief Find the Rubik's Cube
OK OK OK Don't worry about the Rubik's Cube
You can leave quickly, Feiyangyang
Bingbing Sheep This energy cube is very important and cannot be played casually
If you take the energy cube to the village chief
It would be great if you accidentally have the equipment!
Bingbing Sheep, give the energy cube to your brother
I'll help you and give the village chief
If you play with me, I will give you
good
I'll play with you
I can't do it anymore...
Help me see, I'll catch butterflies
Kung fu is not a must!
But...how can I get the equipment?
I remember when Pleasant Goat gained abilities
Difficult to do it?
Come out my equipment!
Is it difficult... Is it difficult to be my posture right?
Let's try it in a few more positions
Come out! I! of! Install! Preparation
Come out... Come out...
No reaction at all
The village chief said that if you encounter problems, you must read more books.
The answer must be in the book
I can't understand at all!
Ahhhhhhhh!
It's the sound of the silly goat!
Sheep and sheep
Don't be afraid that I'm coming!
Really
Don't have to be so loud when you fall, right?
Yes, there's also Pleasant Goat
It seems that I can't help anything
I'm picking fruits and eating
Suddenly a layer of ice was found here
That's how I slipped
Ice?
Why did a layer of ice be collected here?
I did it!
danger!
This… is this?
Is Big Big Wolf controlled by bacteria again?!
Hand over the Bingbing Sheep!
Run quickly! …
Wow! What a big refrigerator
Haha I found you!
Bingbing sheep!
You will run away with the Bingbing Sheep!
I'll hold him back!
Don't expect to succeed!
Not finished yet!
Hahahahahaha
What should I do here?
Be obediently and surrender!
Hand over the Bingbing Sheep!
Your opponent is me
Let it go!
Disappeared?!
A great opportunity!
Humph I've expected it long ago!
You know my s**t is hurt! Ha ha
I...is nothing...
It's so cold...No, I'm going to catch a cold...
There is a broken bit!
I'm the germ king
You're taking action again!
Pleasant Goat...
So what if you are fast
It’s not that there’s no way to deal with me!
Everyone, hide!
Sheep and goat...
Bingbing is so fast
You still have time to worry about others
Let's see how you escape!
Boiling sheep...! !
Brother Feiyangyangyang...
No one stopped me now!
Come with me obediently!
Brother Feiyangyangyang...
Why…
My friend was hurt, but I could only look at him with silence...
If I were strong enough...
I want to protect my friends too
What's going on!
What is this?
Stop me
Not finished yet
Is this my equipment? Feeling hot all over the body, it's hard to tell...
How could this happen!
It seems that my equipment can generate high temperature energy
Boiling Yangyang, let’s defeat him together!
Don't be too proud
There are so many people who come here!
Don't forget that I'm still there!
Very hot, very hot
The most irritating thing is...!
I will definitely come back!
The boiling sheep is so terrible!
Where is this?
Wake up and feel sore
Big Big Wolf, you're controlled by bacteria again
what!
You want to be as clean as me
I won't be controlled!
It seems that the safety system needs to be upgraded...
Boiling sheep!
exist!
Even though you have the equipment now
But the greater the ability, the greater the responsibility
What do you think about this?
Even though I have the equipment now
But what's more important is
Regardless of the size of the ability
Everyone needs to have a heart to help others!
nice!
Boiling Sheep Come and help!
Come!
Help me with hot water!
Help me with hot towels!
Help me have fun!