Boiling Sheep Boiling Sheep
Come here
Boiling sheep
What's going on? It's so urgent?
Hide it
What is this?
So many toys?
Why hide it
Say it
It's still one piece away
My Pinning
Pleasant Goat Brother Sorry
She's still young, I want to tolerate her
It doesn’t matter! You keep playing!
Pleasant Goat Brother I'll play skateboarding for you
Can't!
danger! Come down soon!
This is not what you can play with this toy!
My remote control
Balls are not played like this, either...
These are my remaining toys
I don't want to be damaged by her again
Don't worry
I will protect this light for you
Then please
no!
I must use the most scientific method
Find the cause of the failure
Want to have empty bottle spirit, please tell me the result!
What does this mean?
Could it be...Great Wolf?
The new invention of Big Big Wolf
Can I help me with a failure in repelling?
Ha ha ha ha…
With this...
When a son learns, he won't hurt his eyes
Next, test the ultimate weapon against bacteria
Super 100% energy glue!
Can you glue it?
As long as the bacteria step on this piece of super energy gel
He's too dying
whee
Oops...
Or improve it
well…
It turns out that Big Big Wolf is the reason for my failure
I have to find a stronger body!
Pleasant Goat Brother, let's push the stool together
You can play it yourself
Let's take a picture together
You can paint it yourself
Let's sweep together
You can just swipe yourself I'm working in the industry and I'm very busy!
oh!
What is this? !
That's my kettle! Can't play!
Let's play hide and seek
It's too simple to catch you
Hahaha
Come and catch me!
It's so fun!
Hahaha
Let's see how you hide!
This kettle is very important and cannot be played with by you
I want…
Who is more harmful to find?
Wow
What a sharp claw, you're the one!
What a dangerous
What a strong and powerful corner!
The impact force must be very high!
Let me come and try it!
How bad is rhino horns destroyed!
Hahaha…
Can't pull it out
no!
This is a mess
Have to look for it again
What a sharp spike
I'm here!
It hurts so much
It turns out that Big Big Wolf is already very good...
Look at my improved version of Wanneng Plug!
All can glue!
Deformed...turned into a candle!
Turned into a wall!
Perfect!
It seems that Big Big Wolf is OK!
Dad, mom, sorry
I've left you for my horns to get damaged...
Pleasant Goat Brother...I
Pleasant Goat Brother
sorry
I don't need your apology
Whether it is a toy or a jingle, you have been ruined by you
What's the use of apologizing now! ! !
I just want to...
Want to play with you...
Want to play with me...
I've done this just too much
Ahhhhh!
Bingbing sheep...
Finally, you can unseal
I'll be able to regain my abilities soon
Hahaha...
Let her go! Don’t control Big Big Wolf anymore!
Think beautifully!
It seems that you have to remove the remote control first!
Give up! It's impossible for you to get close to me!
Just wait for my ability to unblock it!
I won't let you succeed!
No one has slammed me now!
Hahaha! !
Pleasant Goat Brother!
You are such a bad egg, please let go of Brother Pleasant Goat!
Bingbing sheep...
Let him go!
Stop it! Otherwise, let's see how I deal with you
No!
I won't let you hurt Bingbing Sheep
My remote control!
You don't have a remote control
I will definitely come back!
Pleasant Goat Brother
Your kettle!
sorry
I shouldn't ruin your tins and toys
I'm wrong, too. I shouldn't be angry with you.
Let's make up
Then do you want to play with me?
OK, but I have to love toys in the future
We hook
I thought about how to fix the ginger
Brother Yangyang, come and help me
Sticky
It seems like a new one
thank you
strangeness? How could I be here?
Hahaha......
Boiling Sheep Boiling Sheep
Pleasant goat?
How did you come?
I'll get my toys back
Well…
This is your most important treasure
Are you not afraid of being damaged by her?
I promised that Brother Pleasant Goat will not get hurt anymore
The most important thing is to play together
You wait
And for you
My baby
Boiling sheep!
You promised to help me keep them well!
sorry! I didn't mean to get rid of it!
Hahaha!
Brother Pleasant Goat Come on!