I haven't found the trace of Brother BB Goat yet
That's the village chief?
Village Chief
You're not looking for it in the laboratory
I want to move some daily necessities to the test room
Then don't run away
Oh my waist...
It's okay I can
Village Chief, please give it to us!
I'm so sorry, I'm sorry for you
Then please move all these things over
So many...
Let us boys come
Thank you Sparky
BB Goat, don't run away
I'll help you too!
Tibbie, let's move things
BB Goat, please ask you
good! Leave it to me!
Where is BB Goat?
BB Goat Come back!
Don't run away with the snail!
It’s you who runs away!
I've failed in my behavior before
This time, you need to control an inconspicuous person
Swimming and fitness
Let's find out about beauty
Swimming, fitness, yoga, dance, free trial
There is also a little fitness class!
So serene, everyone ignored him
Also covered in smelly sweat
You will decide it is you!
ah…
This body is really powerful
But it smells so smelly
I love clean bacteria...
I don't care!
No one will pay attention to me this time
Wait for me
BB Goat, wait for me!
Sister Mei, look!
Can't!
You'll get it like this!
I'm holding it like this
It won't be overwhelmed!
Flying away again
BB Goat If you catch it like this, it will hurt it
It's a snail
If you run away, I will be angry!
Sister, look, it's a snail
Look, look, look
Don't move, I'll pull you up
Very tired
Just catch this guy
You can force BB Goat to find out the whereabouts
So stern...
Do stretching exercises first
If a tiger doesn’t show any power, are you a sick cat?
Catched!
What have you caught?
Of course it is...
Brother Tai, do you want to help me move a chair?
Still moving a chair?
Brother Tai
Isn't this guy very inconspicuous?
Why do the lambs know him?
This little thing! I'll help you!
Thank you brother Tai
Brother Tai, you are so good!
How embarrassed that!
Are you really embarrassed?
That's good too
Take action when the appropriate time
Completed! !
Very tired
It's all up to Brother Tai to complete it so quickly!
Thank you Brother Tai!
No need for a guest...
Village Chief! ?
I didn't expect it to be a little bit...
I'll just stay this one
You can move the rest of your troubles back
I'm so sorry...
what!
BB Goat! Are you okay?
It's so scary here!
Not afraid we're just in the cave
Sister protects you
What is that
There are so many stars!
This is not a star
They are called firecrackers and will shine in the darkness of the night
Why does it stop in your hands?
As long as you're good to them
They will also be happy to be friends with you
So beautiful!
Is it leaving?
It seems like it wants to give us a way. Let's follow us quickly.
There are so many squids here
I'm going to make friends with the squid!
All of them are amazing!
Yes, but at the same time they are also very fragile
We must not harm them
Brother Tai has really helped me a lot...
Oh, what are you doing in Yang Village?
I heard you came here with a kid
See if she is interested in participating in my children's fitness class
Unfortunately, she went out with Tibbie
what! !
Why didn't you say it earlier
This has caused me to move for so long!
Paddi!
Brother Tai, what are you doing
Can't be controlled by bacteria? !
Since you've been discovered, take them all away
We're on!
Ha ha! You can let the bacteria go! !
Or is it Weslie and Sparky
what! !
Brother Tai is too strong
Fortunately, BB Goat is not here
We're back!
Tibbie!
Have you finished moving?
Be careful behind it!
Tibbie!
BB Goat! !
Finally caught you!
BB Goat! BB Goat!
Where did BB Goat be caught by the Bacteria King?
It's all my fault that I didn't protect BB Goat
No...Tibbie!
You can't blame you for this! It's all that...
Where did BB Goat go...
Who can tell me
You see the butterflies shining
This is...
Not just a butterfly
The whole forest is shining
It’s this Daoguang again!
This is...
Come with me quickly. BB Goat is here!
Come with me, everyone, BB Goat is here!
Tibbie How do you know where BB Goat is?
It was the Butterfly who told me!
I mean it!
I won't say much about it
Let me unseal it!
stop!
Keep BB Goat tightly open!
Just you want to resist my speed and strength
Is the perfect combination of flesh?
Brother Tai is really too bad
Last time I was just a careless moment!
I will definitely not return this time! We're on!
No matter how many times the results are
Are you the only level?
You don't have any ability
Don't go and add trouble to Weslie...
Do you think that keeping hiding can defeat me?
Too naive
Weslie!
Being too
It's over
This... what's this
All of them are rolled out for me!
Wow! All the snails are here!
Thank you everyone! I'll help me to help me with one more time
The ability to acquire by Tibbie
Can you communicate with Kuncai to control Kuncai? ?
There are also Tibbie
This is
Since he is a bacteria
I understand
Do you dare to come? !
If this guy is washed clean
I can't control it anymore
Sparky!
The warm water is coming
Very... Comfortable...
It's so comfortable to take a bath...
You wait for me! I will definitely come back!
Come and play next time ~
Tibbie, you have also obtained the equipment
This time it’s all up to Tibbie!
This time it's all up to them
Thank you!
Thank you for your hard work. Come and have a cake
Very good! Have a cake to eat!
It actually snatched my cake! Don't let it go!
Sister Mei said that you should not harm the worm!
The thorn is a bad thorn. You need to take it away
Can't
Scarlet Cracks Take it away!