You can find Bingbing Sheep's brother with confidence
printing? !
It seems that I saved a lot before, and I can change the big cake in just ten.
Go back and look for it
whee……
Do you want to try the goat?
No ~
Don't do this
Look...
Eight outlet hand washes
Just click to wash your hands at the same time
But we don't have 8 people
Look at this very long swipe
A single key can stretch
Easy to help you sweep up to ten meters away
But our family is not that big
It's OK
I also have this gentle chicken hairy croaker!
It will lose hair if you use it too hard
Remind you to treat your furniture with gentleness
OK OK OK OK I accept it all!
I remember to give me a good review of what I used happily!
OK
It is important to me! Remember to give me a good review!
Only the best deals with the sheep left
Bingbing Sheep I'm here
Print Print
Get it right away
I got the handprint immediately
This room is too dirty
It doesn't fit me with clean bacteria
Too scary
It's you again, little
Let's play together
The kids are so noisy
So dirty!
I love clean bacteria
I'll come back to clean up you
Don't go
Too noisy, Bingbing Sheep is quiet!
Bingbing Sheep, you can't run out
Brother Yangyang
Very dirty!
Go and wash your hands!
Go quickly... Go wash your hands
Don't use this hand wash!
It's really not worry-free
Brother, look!
Lots of snowflakes
snowflake!
This is not a toy
How to sweep the chicken hairs with this full of ground
Brother Swatch Swatch!
Don't swipe!
How did it grow
Bingbing sheep!
Go and take a shower
I'm back again
Why is it more dirtier than before?
After taking the handprint, leave quickly
Dry your body before going out
Come back
It turns out that it's so dirty at home
It seems a big shot
It's a print!
The print was found
Flowers?
Let's continue to look for this flower, right?
Flowers Flowers!
Flowers
Another one has been found!
Put on the quilt
Eight and Nine! The last one is missing
We can change the big cake!
Collected prints
The house is clean again
What a happy day today
Thank you for your hard work after being beaten for so long
Let's have a good rest together
It's easy to use for cleaning sets
Remember to give me a good review!
Big Wolf Your cleaning suits...
Hahaha
My cleaning set is very useful
Very clean
Close your mouth! I want to give you your cleaning set
This…
snort
Your stuff
I'll give it to you!
Could it be that my invention has brought trouble to people?
I can't eat it anymore
What happened to me...
I will definitely get the handprint this time!
Eat the porridge
This is a mouth, not a s**t
oops
Flowers
ah!
What sound?
Why are you upset again
No
Stop being cunning
Always fail!
A spider! ! ! !
Bingbing Sheep
I see where you escape this time
elder brother? !
I'll clean up again
elder brother!
So what!
Bingbing sheep!
Let go of the ice sheep!
Is my invention really useless?
Go open!
what? !
It's you again? ! Is Bingbing Sheep caught?
Bingbing Sheep
Let go of the Bingbing Sheep
Bingbing Sheep, you're fine
What's going on
Flowers
Bingbing sheep! You'll come back soon
I'm here to help
Use hand sanitizer to clean the spider
The bacteria cannot be controlled!
good
Can't be shot anymore Look at me
ah!
See you again haha
Think about it quickly if there are any other ways
Have it!
Use a swipe to help you catch up with the spider
Hurry up!
You said you were chasing with a stick, you didn't want me to fly?
Another one?
Why do you want to catch the spider without putting it?
Let go quickly
Get it
Bingbing sheep! ! ! !
Bingbing sheep!
Bingbing sheep! ! !
I…
Haven't you changed back?
I have the equipment, too?
Bingbing sheep!
Bingbing Sheep
You're fine
You're okay, my ability is to attract things?
Give me some little things!
ah!
I will definitely come back!
Brother Yangyang
Flower Flower Flower Flower
fool
I just want to help me get the prints when I chase the bacteria
Brother's Flowers
thank you
I'm here to save you, sheep!
The print you said changed this cake
No
These prints have special recollections
I won't change it
You still eat what I made
and
Big Wolf Thank you
I didn't expect your cleansing invention
Helped to save Bingbing Sheep
My cleaning set is still very useful
But just do it
snort
Wait, I'll find something more useful next time
I'm looking forward to it
We're back
Pleasant Goat Goat Have you found Bingbing Goat’s brother?
No
Then let's continue to find it tomorrow
What's your hand
It's my new installation!
New installation!
What happened? Tell us now!
Cough cough
On a dark morning