Leave school, leave school
I'll go to buy cakes when the store is closed
Class Manager
I'm going to stay for the day today
Can you help me take Bingbing Yang to play?
Hello Sister Jonie!
OK!
Thank you, the class leader
Play with Bingbing Yang
Class Manager
I'm in a hurry to buy something, can you help me with flowers?
Of course it's OK
Thank you, the class leader
Chief!
Sparky
There will be a basketball game. Can you send me a letter?
Ball game
All right
Then I'll leave first
Running so fast
Not much
After completing these, you can buy the cake
Can the class leader send me a express delivery?
Class Manager
Thank you, the class leader
Thank you for helping the small aircraft to hand over
Accompany Brother Tai to exercise
Sweep the mother Niu
Help Mr. Monkey move
Why
Next
Why do you have so many things to do
Forget it, come one by one
Let's go play Bingbing Yang
good!
Why can I beat me every time!
no
I want to think of a solution
Wolffy! After cleaning the living room, I went out to clean the kitchen
OK! Red
But when should I wash the dirt at this time...
If only it could be cleaned up in one breath
Haji
It's you?
You give me a stand!
I can't catch you yet
Help
No matter what, you can't escape my eight hands
Ha ha ha ha
Help
Eight hands?
Have it!
- If I have eight hands, I will be able to finish my homework soon
What a good idea hahahahaha
Um?
When will I make up with you
It seems that you have to use your dirty body again
What are you talking about?
And so
Wait and see, lamb
Sister Jonie, look
Bingbing Yang, you're so terrible
It's the first thing
Jonie, you can
Bingbing Yang, please wait for my sister here first
good
Finally... Go find Bingbing Yang
Um?
Bingbing Yang Bingbing Yang?
Bingbing Yang is missing!
Huh?
Weslie, don’t you have to go back to accompany Bingbing Yang today?
I have to stay for the day
Just ask the squad leader to play with Bingbing Yang
I also asked the class leader to send a letter!
Then wait a moment, let's thank her together
good
Why are there so many people
They are here too
How are you here
We ask the class leader to help us. I want to thank her for your thanks
But I found out she wasn't here
what! Have you asked her for help?
yes
I...we are too
It turns out that the class leader has done so much...
She must be busy
Why don't we help her
Um
Such a good device is too wasteful to use for sanitation
Or use it to catch Bingbing Yang
What a coincidence I'm looking for you
It's you, uncle
Do you want to play with me?
OK
I'll have fun with you hahahahahahahahaha
Bingbing Yang!
Huhu
Finally found you
So you are here in Wolffy
Sister Jonie
Want to run
Big Wolf What are you doing
Let it go...
Let her go
Wolffy
Not the wolf
It's the germ king!
ah?
It seems that Wolffy is being controlled again
Let go of Bingbing Yang
If you have the ability, come here
ah! !
Hahahahaha
Are you too weak or am I too bad
Just want to stop me, do you want to stop me?
Even if I'm the only one
I won't, either
I won't... let you hurt Bingbing Yang!
what!
I have a set-up, but how do I use it?
what? !
So many!
But... so small
What are you talking about?
Who are you talking about
What's going on
It should be the power of the energy stone
Great, I have the equipment, too
yeah! Great, great, great!
Very good! Great, great
Why don't we go and save Bingbing Yang first
good!
Push, Push, Push, Push
What a joke
Spread it out soon!
ah......
Why did they all collide?
You didn't say where to disperse
kindness
Let me tell you
Hahahahaha
I won't play with you anymore
Wolffy?
What are you doing this?
It's you again!
It seems I have to start first
The Paddi The Paddi!
Let me go
It seems that Big Wolf is controlled again
careful
Useless
My invention is to restrain your abilities
Don't want to run
That's now!
Hehehehehehehe
I've seen my eight-handed s**t
Let me go
Can't move anymore
It depends on who can stop me
stop
It's the class leader
Is it dazzled me? The class leader seems to be getting smaller
It's you again
Haven't been trained?
Plan begins
What...what
Why are there two more class managers
Another one appears here
Rescue first and then say
I didn't expect that the clone's strength was still the same as before
Successful rescue of the Goat
good!
Good thing to hurt me
Since my equipment is ineffective for you
Then I will use my own strength to stop you
How did he escape?
Sparky  rescued successfully
It's you!
You guys!
Get out of Wolffy
All rescued successfully
good
You're nowhere to escape. The King of Bacteria
Don't play with you anymore
Bingbing Yang
Oh no, he ran away
And me
You'll wait for me
It's okay
Thank you Sister Jonie
So that's how it is
That means the class leader is the same as us
Yes, I will be able to use my clone in the future
Class Manager
We were bad before, so we asked you to do so much
sorry
So we won't be like this in the future
Nothing, I'm very happy to help you
The class leader…
You are so good!