Sister Tibbie Come and play with me
Wow, Sister Tibbie is so terrible
Oh, it's a mosquito
mosquito? I want to play with you!
BB Goat can't play with mosquitoes!
Mosquitoes are harmful to the
No, Mosquito wants to play with me!
Still too small, I don't know how to be afraid
As far as I can see
Mosquitoes may be more scared
Is your name Xiao Wuwu?
I need you if you have a unique mosquito inventories
You will participate in the mosquito inventories competition in three days
If I participate in the competition...
But my face was stinged
That was traumatized by you...
Yes, I can make an inventorial mosquito
This creature called mosquito
It seems to make them feel very irritated
Huh? Why does it hurt a little?
You dare to bite me, the germ king!
Do you want to do?
Don't be afraid I just want to cooperate with you
Do you understand what I say?
Of course I am the germ king!
You are not enough...
Little buzz, are you hungry?
I'll find you something to eat
Little Buzz Do you not eat ice cream?
Then I'll eat it
How long does BB Goat need to keep this mosquito?
We can't stand it anymore
It seems like I want to try to eliminate him
But BB Goat is so baby mosquito, there is no chance to
How to open BB Goat
My hands are dirty
I'm going to the bathroom
I'll take you to wash your hands
Are you doing?
Why did you scare the little buzzer?
BB Goat We just...
The residents of the grassland are too much
Always deal with us in various ways!
My brother fell under their mosquito coils
And my nephew was slapped by them.
My second uncle was also beaten to death by them with slippers
Well
It seems to be in the wrong venue
so
We're going to organize
I have strong body, I want to be a team leader
I'm flying fast I'm going to be a team leader
I am the leader! I am I am!
What a fat mosquito
Look at how round his belly and how hard his wings are
It looks like a wealthy family!
I'm the captain. What's the problem?
no!
Then come out!
The first one to be arrested was the group of goat
Wait a moment!
Wolffy seems to be doing something about mosquitoes
Wolffy made a destructive invention
Depart!
Brother Weslie, I'll tell you!
We are for your own good!
And I'm a little buzzing!
But the little buzzer has already run away
Look, the little buzz is flying back
Little buzz!
Why are there so many mosquitoes
Weslie Brother Let it open!
Be careful, there is something wrong
Mosquito Team Two, I'm so excited!
Leave it to me
ah
I'll talk about mosquitoes!
One team gave me the leader!
Little buzz!
I want to play with Xiaobubu!
Such many mosquitoes will hurt you
But Xiao Wuwu is my friend!
What's going on?
I'm back at the bathroom
Why are there so many mosquitoes
Help!
Don't be afraid
This is my invention
We don't have that? The long tongue...
Next
My method is to use singing to move mosquitoes
It's
ah
It hurts so much!
Isn't there any invention like this?
I have!
The moment of witnessing the strange moment has come
What's the difference between this and our own hands?
Your hands are too small and you can only take one at a time
But my invention is different
Everyone……
Don't interfere with competitions
How many can my robot take pictures!
This……
There!
Very awesome, very awesome!
This is what you forced me!
Let me stimulate the potential of this mosquito!
The small buzz has become bigger
It turns out that it's caused by bacteria. Run away
Brother Weslie, you're fine!
It's OK
Mosquitoes are harmful to sucking blood
It will be very dirty after being bitten
Brothers and sisters just don't want to let mosquitoes
Still have time to worry about others?
Little buzz! Why do you hurt Brother Weslie
Hahaha I just like it!
Humph My invention is to shoot mosquitoes
Your invention is still useless
I have many more tricks!
Mosquito coils ejaculate!
Mosquito water launch!
He flew too fast and couldn't spray him
Wolffy help me throw it behind him
no problem!
Where are you throwing it?
Look at mine
Don't you know
Mosquitoes are very agile hahaha
You are not my opponent at all!
What are you laughing at
And me! Super mosquito drive water!
Big Wolf Thank you
Don't be civil!
Very cruel!
I'll give you a paste when I go back
Will you still have mosquitoes in the future?
Sorry, I won't play with mosquitoes again
They are bad people
What's your name? I want to play with you!
No way