Red Red takes his son back to his parents' home
I can do my experiments with it
hey-hey! The female devil is gone
Hand over your body obediently. Big Grey Wolf
Wolffy I'm here!
You want to control me again!
This is your blessing
I... I'm defiled! !
Wolffy No one is more dirty than you
Now go wash my hands immediately!
No one is more troublesome than you
Disappear for me immediately!
Who is it! ?
Big Wolf We're here
Why did so many wolves suddenly come
Can't be discovered...
What did you come...
It was Wolnie who called us
She said you've been talking to the wall lately
Unexplained vitality
I'm afraid you're in a bad mood, so I'll ask us to accompany you
It must have been seen by Wolnie during the quarrel
No need to welcome us, we can do it ourselves
How can you take this as your home?
Wolffy Where is the phone?
Wolffy Where are you? ?
Don't quarrel with me, you can watch it yourself
It's so terrible
Can't I take a serene experiment?
Tolerance is beyond your reach! You made me have a real experience!
Can you be at ease? ?
Do you want to tear my house down? !
You're too much!
Why! Unable to communicate...
Go back and have a practical experience...
What are you going to do you?
Do you want to buy a facial mask?
I... don't
There is a smile mask
Very suitable for you
No
Do you want to look at other things like this
There is a pearl mask, rainbow door mask and clown mask
There must be something suitable for you
Buy two and get one free
Where is Wolffy?
Can't stand it anymore
I'm going to call Wolnie and let them go back
Hello! Forrest Gump, have you finished watching the cross-time and space rescue?
There are sixty episodes in total
Last time we talked about episode 5
Nothing is OK
It doesn't matter how long it takes to chat
Oops No more
Have you seen it? Isn't it very bad?
It's super wonderful there!
OK, look at it slowly, see again!
Finally finished
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
In comparison, the bacteria are much more tranquil
Wolffy, you have today too!
Very hungry
First go to the kitchen to get some food and come back and then look forward to the food
So many wolves
Which one to catch the iced goat?
Who is it!
Who dares to be so arrogant!
What's going on...
Why did this guy hide here to paint
It's so dirty
The refrigerator is still so far away...
It seems that I can only take risks!
If you want to hit the king like this, do you want to hit the big king?
Haha...hahaha...hahahaha!
Easy to go
What's going on this time! !
It's so noisy outside, I'm still here to make clay guys
Yes...and it's also very spiritual
Really worthy of being an artist...
This is not a kitchen, a battleground!
The end is right in front! I'm already scared!
Just practice here
In comparison...
Wolffy is much cleaner
These wolves are dirty
I will control them and go home
Start with the most unhealthy beginning!
He actually hid!
ah
Forget it and go control him!
ah!
There is actually a snail!
So dirty!
This time you must succeed!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Help!
What is this...
This washing machine is good. Make a mark and I will take it away
ha?
The quality of this phone is good, I took it away!
Both are like this...
You will give me a message! !
By the way, Wolffy...
Say it well...
It's so fun to have fun here
I almost forgot to send it to you
They are all specialties from their hometown
Isn't this mud statue very realistic?
I've been doing it for three days and three nights
I've painted a portrait for you
Everyone…
Yes, what are you just saying
Uh... nothing
You can't finish eating this much
Let's help you eat
It's too difficult for them to rush away
Unless you want to let them go by themselves
Go by yourself?
There is a way, but two people need to cooperate
Happy cooperation...
ah! !
Who is calling out
I'm going to sleep and I'm going to deal with him!
A monster has entered the Wolf Castle! ! Come quickly
You're sleeping poorly! !
No...it's true!
Look, why are you foggy?
I still think I'm in danger
I'll read the storybook to upload
Usually, the monster will appear in this way
Ahhh! !
What is it called! I was scared!
Will this darkness open the light? !
You are really the faces of the Wolf tribe
Look how calm I am!
What sound is this?
What a deep scratch
There are also big footprints
What kind of monster is it
What's scary, too
Ahhhhhh
It's Big Wolf's voice
We'll save him
Wolffy!
ah! ! !
Hello! Didn’t you come to save me? !
They should have been scared to run away now
We're back!
Wait a moment!
What a do! ?
I... it's late
I'll go to the bottom of the monster first
Wolffy... How can you be a cannon fodder?
Be careful
Monster, I've fought with you
ah
Wolffy I'll come to help you!
No... Don't rush, calm!
Too scary
Run
Finally left
Ah, I forgot about the wolf! !
How could we give you up?
Second uncle
I didn't expect you to love me
It's so despicable, my face was scared
This helper looked at this rough
Unexpectedly, there was still some emotion
This time, this king recognizes you
This cooperation is still quite successful
The "monster" played by King Tatsumoto is realistic
What are you talking about?
It was obviously a great show I played in front of them!
Hello
Big Wolf, you're fine
When we got home, we found out that we had carried a statue and left!
You... don't you blame us, do you? …
It's okay, just be able to go back safely
Then see again
Who is plotting against this king!
It's really hard to stand it
Please give me clean
I can't kill a wolf
No, too dirty
unless…
Someone can help me
It actually made this king help me to sweep
I won't let you go!
I almost forgot to wash the red skirt
I've solved it for you
Are you saying you've washed?
It's already thrown away, too dirty
Throwed it?
How did you throw away the red skirt?
Yes, it's too dirty
That's her favorite skirt
Where did you throw her skirt? Say it quickly!
Don't know the trash can
Retrieve me back
You actually dare to dirty this king!
I'm not going to be with you! !
Go out of my castle! Make a dream! Look at the trick!