Be careful!
Don't leave!
BB Goat, can't you be at ease?
Can't eat anything wrong
Don't lie on the ground, either
So tired...
BB Goat...
Just let me go and let me sleep for a while!
All right......
Then I'll go out to play!
BB Goat Come back soon
It's very dangerous outside...
You're too tight
It's normal for a child to stumbling
Oops!
Haven't been hurt! Injury infection will cause irritation!
The tightest one is obviously you, the village chief…
Village Chief!
What is this?
I've been to BB Goat
Made a robot that protects her
"Safety Baby"
Safe bag?
Give me down!
Smell germs! Hiding in my house all day!
You come out to me
Do you think I can't find you if you hide it?
yes
I can't find mine
Um?
Bacterial tracking cannon! !
Target locked!
Launch!
It depends on where you run! Hahahahahaha!
Cough cough cough
I didn't expect this to be quite terrible
Since you've fallen
Then I'm not polite...
Hahaha Come and chase me!
Is this really useful?
Don't worry
He has infused all my energy
It also has automatic upgrade function
Make safety protection more and more perfect!
Is this thing a simplified...
Chase me!
Chase me quickly!
careful!
Removal of danger
So terrible!
What a bad thing! …
danger!
Confirm safety and remove danger
You know what I invented is a big deal!
yes! yes! Very terrible! …
Updated list of dangerous items
Fruit peel is dangerous...
Safe Baby let's go out and play!
The lamb must be very difficult
Be extra careful...
Come and catch me. Catch me!
BB Goat?
Been caught! Been caught!
I didn't expect to catch it so simply!
Let go of BB Goat!
warn!
If you don’t let BB Goat goat open, you will launch an attack!
Attack my germ king?
Just hate you as a broken robot?
Wolf Danger!
I won't give up!
Goat Dangerous!
Lollipops Small pit danger!
danger! danger!
danger!
It was that robot that damaged me again...
Glow... Glow is so angry!
What's the matter again!
Yes
Success
You can't escape the robot!
Look at me using the super coach transformed by alien technology to blow you up!
Have a meal
Wow
I'm here!
BB Goat! Come and have a grass ball!
danger! danger!
What's going on? ! !
Successfully eliminate dangerous objects
BB Goat is in danger!
Turn off the cancellation mode Enable rescue mode
Fruit sauce cartridge!
Can't let him destroy the goat village!
BB Goat handed me over!
He was caught by Brother Weslie!
danger!
A piece of cake ~
And we!
Now playing wooden game with you
It's gone when it moves
knew
Don't forget me
No! Another
It depends on where you run away!
Robot I'm here to take revenge!
What's going on?
BB Goat!
No! The gun is out of control!
Run quickly!
I don't move! It's gone when it moves!
Danger...relieve...
You know my s**t is hurt!
It's soaring... BB Goat will give you...
I'll leave first
I'll catch BB Goat
actually……
Safety bags work very well
It's all up to his protection. BB Goat was not injured.
BB Goat!
Does it hurt?
pain……
Then remember that I can't get upset, do you know?
knew
You can't pick up anything on the ground and eat it
My stomach hurts after eating
Look, I just said you're too tight...
Children cannot grow up beyond nursing
It seems that I'm the most tight