Dry lights won't get sick
What happened
Is the end of the world?
Red and Wilie went on a trip
I'm sick again
How many days did it take to be like this?
Can you help me swipe it?
Want my expensive germ king to help you with a swipe? No door!
Little ghost!
snort! I'm going to catch goat!
I can't stand it anymore!
I have to control him to clean it!
Just repair your nails
I need to apply a facial mask if my face is so dry...
Cleanliness is so confident!
Not good, it's too clean, it can't be controlled
He actually dared to expel the king...
What a big s**t!
Haha... Sorry...
Um? The nose seems to be clear
The fire seems to have retreated!
Sorry, don't be angry
Why are you turning white?
Ah...
This…
What happened to this
Finish!
With this detector
It can determine whether the cleanliness of the visitor is controlled by bacteria
Once the visitor is detected, it is controlled by sterilization
The detector will immediately launch a water cannon to attack
Is it really useful?
Now let's show you
It's okay to walk past without being controlled like me
Like that kind of dirty...
not good!
The village chief was controlled by bacteria!
Don't be tight
There was only a problem with the setting. Just reinstall it
Fixed
Very good!
Have a letter...
The Bacteria King is here!
What's going on? I'm just here to send a letter...
But the village chief's detector detected
Your cleanliness is less than 10%
I've just been a little busy lately and forgot to take a shower for a few days...
I'm so sorry, Brother Rabbit
It seems that there are still loopholes in the detector. I need to change it...
I said you...what do you want to do me?
benefactor
Thank you for your care
I'll take care of you?
You live in and eat with me and chat with me...
look
You helped me again, I want to report it
Is there anything else to help?
The window should be wiped...
Anyone need help?
The warehouse needs to be cleaned!
The floor needs to be towed!
Anyone need help?
No more...
no! I can't help it
I'll go outside to see if I need anything else to help me!
What happened...
The road is blocked. What should I do?
Don't act—
It turns out you are helping me...
Thank you
What the hell is going on?
Help!
It's okay? Do you need me to help you?
No... nothing
Thank you
Report a mysterious person
Help those in need on the grassland
Wonderful of everyone's love
Who is this mysterious person who is happy to help others?
Come quickly everyone
I've reinstalled
This time, it will only cause bacteria
No harm or innocent
Is there anything to help?
But why did the detector not respond?
I don’t believe it, I can’t repair you well!
Village Chief is not the time to care about this problem now
We want to protect Bingbing Yang!
Where has Bingbing Yang gone? ?
I'll help you!
It's good enough!
It's you again! Leaving Bingbing Yang far away!
good
Why did he become white?
I must be playing some tricks!
Don't fight Don't fight
He's no longer a mess
Look, everyone
It turns out that he is the one who often helps people on the grassland!
Good man please help me sign a name
Please accept our gifts. Great guy
What happened this?
I don't know either
He helped me take a shower and it turned out like this...
See you again
goodbye!
I want to go to the universe to help more creatures!
Hajiu-
Is he really leaving?
I thought he was a bad guy
I didn't expect others to be good
I took out all the rockets from my house
Thank you, benefactor!
Thank you everyone!
I will continue to help with your encouragement and love!
This is my gift I wish you peace and prosperity
I won't forget yours! goodbye
See you again See you again!
Why didn't the village chief come?
The village chief has been from yesterday to now
Have been repairing his detector
I dare not slap him
Thank you for your relationship during this period
Let us become good friends
Even though I can't let you go
But you have dreams and want to realize
Then I will be far away as a friend and wish you a blessing
Although this Rocket was my long time ago, goat-catching inventor
I hope it can accompany you through every corner of the universe on my behalf
Also, I found you have a cold
I specially prepared a bottle of cold tea for you
Remember to drink it!
Wolffy is so good to me! Hajiu-
Finally, there is no need to worry about the danger of our Bingbing Yang!
Look, the Rockets are back!
The great guy is back! He must also want to continue to help us
You guys
Do you still want me to help me?
The good guy has changed! Escape quickly!
Why did he change again!
What gift did you give to the bacteria
It made his temperament become like this!
Wolffy! Your cold tea is delivered in a timely manner
It cured my cold!
Otherwise I'll never be under control
It turns out that I saved him...
It turns out that he will become a good person after catching a cold
Bingbing Yang are almost released!
I'll fly
No matter how fast I am, I can't fly to heaven!
What's going on! ?
I just said that my invention will not be useless!
I've not only expanded the test scope
I've increased the range of water columns, too
I will never let go of the bacteria in the sky!
Taste the Rockets meal that this king gave you!
Wow!
snort! Such a helper dares to do this to me!
Let's see how I teach them!
Ha chi!
Wolffy! What do you want to do?
Why haven't you been infected by me yet?
For the universe, for the grassland!
I've had a few cold showers
Make yourself sick!
How often do I get sick is one in a million
I'll let you die of this heart
One in ten?
Then I'm not catching a cold for nothing?