Ten Miles of Flourishing Sweet and Flourishing
It's worthy of being the drink that Wolffy likes
What's going on?
You must have caused a bunch of mosquitoes
Let me go quickly
This is true
I dare to savor the king of the country tasted this delicious drink
This taste...
It's disinfectant!
Swallow it!
What disinfectant is sprayed! It won't let anyone live anymore!
Not allowed!
good
I'm leaving!
You beg me, I won’t come back!
Small bacteria
Please!
I can't let me go, right
mistaken!
Please don’t come back when you leave! ! !
To prevent the spread of mosquitoes
Everyone is going home to sweep
I'll check it out later
good
It's so tiring to fight
Let's sleep first and replenish your energy
Little beef
Do you want to go up and find a companion?
I'll help you.
OK, go to bed
This is much more comfortable than the Wolf Castle ceiling!
Just live here!
Disinfection water!
If I could recover my abilities
I just want a home
Why is that difficult?
No one
Just live here!
Why is it so dirty?
Thank you for helping me climb up the tree
Please accept my thank you
Wow! I'm not polite anymore
Paddi
Have you done the swipe?
Almost done
good
I'll check now
If I didn't do a good job of swiping, today's class meal...
Cancel
what
Village Chief, etc.
Village Chief, why not check the others first
Everyone else has checked it, you're the one who's missing
Paddi...
Have a taste, no more class meals
So clean
very good! Health has reached the standard
How could it be so clean?
Good job!
Keep working hard next time!
Who helped me to swipe?
No matter what!
Think about it again if you fill your stomach!
Even if you even take out the trash, you have to run so far! Goat Village is really inconvenient
Finally I can take a break
oops!
Cleared clean
Why is there trash again? ! !
Why is the room clean again?
The garbage on the ground has been cleaned up again
Who is helping me secretly?
It's hard to tell...
Did he find out?
It's you
Sister Bee Niu?
I must have helped you. You came to report it.
I want everyone to come and take a look!
Everyone is here to see Sister Beniu
If Bingbing Yang comes, can I catch her at the opportunity?
no
Wait a little longer
Didn’t he ask everyone to come and see Sister Zhiniu?
All the fruits have been eaten up
I want to wait for Sister Xiniu to buy some back
Treat everyone well
what?
There are fruits
But what if they want to watch a TV?
It's time to hand it over to Sister Viniu
- This is what we see the latest situation!
But I haven't finished writing the work, so I still can't go out.
Do you want me to come in the industry?
There is really Sister Beautiful
Your job is wrong
It seems that this sister Beef has little culture
Is there any sister of the sage?
I'm going to find Sister Xiniu, too
I'll go too
Brother, I'm going to see Sister Beniu
OK
The opportunity is here
Let's go to bed
I'll see Sister Zhiniu helping us to do a family business soon
OK!
Has Sister Zhiniu arrived? Why haven't you come yet?
Don't talk she'll come soon
elder brother!
Don't talk, I'll scare Sister Niu
Where is Bingbing Yang?
Bingbing Yang!
What's up?
Bingbing Yang I don't see it anymore!
what? !
But I was just at the door
There!
Sister Zhiniu Why are you leaving?
What sister is the silly
This is clearly the bacteria control the cattle!
Leave it to me!
hello
Just you want to live with me? !
Don't think about it!
Don't let him run away!
Done beautifully!
The good thing just started!
accelerate!
What happened?
See you again, lamb
The bacteria are about to escape!
Think about it quickly, Weslie!
Have it!
What's the way!
Sparky  is handed over to you!
Humph, do you want to force me out? !
Give me Bingbing Yang!
He actually deceived me. It's not unreasonable!
I failed again...
Sorry, almost let the bacteria catch you
Thank you Brother Baiyangyang for letting me see Sister Bainiu!
Let me taste this drink well
Who?
Please listen to me
What are you talking about?
I'm back!
This is true
Didn’t you say you won’t come back after you’ve finished it? And my drink!
Or is it suitable for me here
I really hope that the real sister of the ox comes out to help me
Is Sister Zhiniu coming?
Bingbing Yang!
My cake