It depends on what you have made my family look like! !
Your house is not very good
I don't want to swear you! !
The king is willing to live in the broken house in the district
-Invasion mode!
Depart!
Get me back with the little one!
Why is it out of control! ?
I've taken a bath eight hundred times
All the body is washed away without any stain
See how you will use our troubles in the future
Do you think it's enough to just guard me alone?
I've notified my good partner has arrived
As long as they arrive
Poop can destroy the entire green grassland!
Can you still have a partner?
Of course!
They are my best partners!
Especially my little yellow!
We've known each other since we were young
At that time
He has something good to me first.
Win the prize! Come another box! !
Xiao Huang is the best for me! !
He is still in a very important single-car competition
He exchanged his beloved warrior to me
That's why I won the championship!
He for me...
Brothers, please! ! Push, Push, Push
You can even have no life
Xiao Huang My best brother...
Are you fricking? Let me go! !
I'm not interested in your story at all
Hello! Pleasant goat?
Oh, right, I made an appointment for you to have a picnic today, wait
The food I prepared was eaten up by the Demon King! !
I'll go and prepare a new one
It’s all the fault of that bacteria king!
I haven't seen such thick face skin!
You have to find a way to walk him away!
who! ?
A piece of cake!
Earthlings
Not enough!
It seems that as long as I join forces with the Bacteria King
You can conquer this place very quickly!
Are you the best partner of the germ king?
That's right
The King's Most Powerful Help...
Don't beat
You know your germ king
I want to destroy you all
Actually, I am not here to help the germ king! !
Are you not good friends for many years?
I've never had a good thing since I followed him
My candy! !
Since it fell to the ground
Then don’t waste money!
Win the prize! !
This time I have a super strong single car
The champion is nothing more than me!
The car is broken! ! ? ?
The king is equipped with a car!
superior! ! !
Rush! Rush!
As long as you frick him, I will be the leader!
Look at me! Iron head skills! ! !
I'm not willing to give up
I'm not willing to accept it. He will always take away good things!
I'm going to take his lead!
So I usually bring this doll around
It's just to remind yourself not to forget this enemy
Yellow sacred
I didn't eat it
He is the new helper for the sterilization king
Amoetic bacteria!
what?
Protect the Bingbing Sheep!
I surrender I surrender! !
I'm not coming back to help him!
I have a bloody hatred with him!
He seems to hate the germ king very much
Are you standing here?
Yes Yes
I'm very bad!
So what skills do you have?
Yes
The Bacteria King said that you were so darn
But I think you are weak
Don't look down on others!
My abilities are so powerful!
As long as I see something
I can change it!
Is this the thing on Earth
Deformation! !
Bounce on the bed! !
Quick change toys change robot change aircraft
It seems that this morphine is not very dangerous
Does Big Big Wolf want to eat something?
Of course!
Glow ball
I won't change anymore! !
- Change the boat Change the bicycle Change the doll
It's so fast that I'll be exhausted
It turns out you are here!
You don't come! ! I won't play anymore! ! I won't play anymore! ! !
Xiao Huang?
Head leader?
It's really you?
Head
We finally met! !
Have you been good lately?
I was just bullied by several wolf and sheep
Have you met them too?
If I weren't sealed
I won't be so depressed by being bullied by the creatures on earth.
seal?
It seems that your appearance is really different
Say long, things are like this
As a result, I was accidentally sealed by Bingbing Sheep
So that's how it is
It seems that this is the best time for me to take revenge!
But
Now with your help
All problems can be solved!
My help?
How many enemies did we faced in the past
Whenever we fall into an absolute situation
Your ability will always make us turn the world
It turns out I
It's so important
now
As long as I unseal
The whole universe belongs to us!
right!
That's right! It's all ours!
Since that's the case
Then wait until you get everything and then snatch it!
Let's go and take revenge!
Xiao Huang, you seem to have lost something
Yes?
No
That…
What is this!
You hear me explain!
You don't need to explain it!
I didn't expect you...
Respect me so much
I also kept my doll around
I'm so broken that I don't want to throw it away...
Good brother!
That's right, I just keep worshiping the head
Let's go! Let's take revenge!
Have you found the morphine?
Didn't see it
We're back! !
Get some small...
Amoetic bacteria!
Where have you been? We're still looking for you!
Let me slide!
What's going on
We have to conquer here!
But didn’t you say you were reporting the germ king before?
Headmaster Don't listen to him nonsense!
You actually...
No, you heard me
You dare to take my face
Give you a look!
Xiao Huang!
Obey the order!
Launch! !
Pleasant goat
Everyone! Please help us!
And me! !
Heat-resistant!?
Fist gloves are right!
Taste me! !
Do you think I am really resistant to high temperatures? !
Hahahaha Yes, sorry
I didn't expect them to be so strong together
OK, I won't play anymore
Keep them clean!
good!
Please agree!
Just gotten too much, I haven't been overwhelmed yet
Do you want to frick?
Will this much be harmful? ?
I will definitely come back! !
Don't learn me to say!
We should go home and have a meal
Then next time
Red I'm back
Why are you here again! !
Hum, unopen the seal
We've been living here!
Who lets you live here!
Strictly let me go!
Who can help me to pull them away! ! !