Translation
Brave Adventurer with Hidden Baby Picture
Arrived at the mysterious cave
The collapsed stone pillar
Terrible traps such as man-cannibal flowers and huge rocks
After some twists and turns, I finally found the precious treasure
Wow, Baozang! I want it too!
That's just the story of the story. It's not true.
There is no treasure, but I have treasure pictures!
No matter how you look, it doesn't look like a hidden treasure
Where did you find it?
It was found under Brother Pleasant Goat's bed...
Under my bed?
Watch it quickly!
Baozang's next stop is here!
This is my shoulder
etc!
Why does my house have a treasure?
Found it!
what?
I never thought you were so naive
Newly found map display line
I have, too?
Found it!
Sister Meiyangyang also has it!
Why does this happen at home?
Finished!
It can really be put together!
Is it hard to know if there is really a treasure?
But
Why doesn’t Sister Nuan Yangyangyang have any?
I don't know either...
Since that's the case
Then let's go and look for it
Very good! Going to treasure!
Lalala! Go to the treasure!
Be careful not to walk too fast!
The cave must be right in front
Wait
It turns out they are going to the cave
I think we had it in that year
Happy? !
Xiao Huang is in danger ahead,
But don't worry! I will protect you!
King ~!
careful!
Xiao Huang is fine
Yes, thank you for saving me
Hahaha It's always OK to follow me!
Xiao Huang! Xiao Huang!
Xiao Huang, don't be afraid, I'll deal with it!
King, what should I do
Fungi: Go here!
That exploration was so happy
You will be happy! It’s me who are injured!
Yes
Just set a trap on their way
It can catch them easily!
Good job! Action now!
You'll encounter monsters right away
Bingbing sheep are here to protect you!
We've all come here. What's the matter? Monsters...
Don't destroy the beautiful imagination of the little girl
Brother and sister
You will encounter monsters immediately!
Bingbing sheep are here to protect you!
This sound...
It's hard to tell! ! !
really…
Brother Qingyangyang stops sleeping. It's very dangerous here
Bingbing Sheep There is nothing here
Why don't we go home and sleep
Look! It's a cave!
The story book says it is deep in the cave
There is really a cave
Brothers and sisters, come quickly!
Bingbing Sheep Slowly
Bingbing sheep!
You're fine
It's okay, everyone be careful
What's going on here...
Maybe it's aging
I have a second trick
I'm secretly on their way
Alien cannibal flowers
Bingbing sheep!
Look at mine
It's a man-cannibal flower, exactly like the story
This is not a time to be happy...
This adventure seems to be getting more and more interesting
Quick
I'm about to find Baozang
They ran away again!
Be careful there will be big rocks in front of you!
How do you know?
That's what the storybook says!
We won't be so easy to recognize
What's going on?
Look at the stone coming
Let's run!
I'll hold on
There's really a rock
That's it!
The impact is too great!
Who can tell me how to escape
Here is here!
Come with me!
Thank you~!
They escaped again
But it's good that we didn't get hurt this time
How can I catch Bingbing Sheep?
If they were treasures
The purpose is to find the treasure box!
I packed it into a treasure box and waited for the iced sheep to come and then...
Good job!
If only there was a treasure
Baozang is something that only children like
I don't care at all
Look!
There is really a treasure!
I'm a kid too
Go over quickly!
You'll catch you right away!
There will be nothing wrong, right?
Go and have a look
Not this
How do you know?
You see
The picture of the hidden treasure is under a tree
Maybe it was because of the Tibetan painting!
trap…?
What should brothers and sisters do? !
It's you!
Could it be that you designed the machine in front?
Now I know it's too late
Bingbing Sheep, run!
Don't let him catch it
Want to run?
Bingbing sheep!
It's you, Uncle Banana
Well done Xiao Huang!
Watch them! I'll be able to unblock it right away!
My hidden treasure pictures!
yes! King!
Bingbing sheep...
Hidden treasure pictures?
They calculated it again!
I'm so angry!
Why don’t you find out the treasure first?
Why can't you move anymore?
Where is the lamb?
Here
You're doing it yourself
etc.
Help...
Stay calm
It will be fine soon!
Let the ice-bing sheep goat open!
Why are you here? What about Xiao Huang?
The King
I failed
How can you be so stupid
Wouldn't you become a small item and escape?
Yes!
Look at me!
This makes you even more unable to get out
Very tired...
Or I'll come back next time!
You wait for me!
I know that bacteria are the stolen
Why do we still have to dig for treasures?
Hum!
Just satisfy Bingbing Sheep's imagination
I dug up the treasure!
This is...
You paint me so cute!
Humph, you can't do much better than me!
Repaint to me
I don't want it!
stop!
Stop me!
Why don't we hide this picture
Wait until you grow up and take it out
This is our treasure picture
Everyone should save it well!
good
It turns out that the hidden treasure picture is real
This is our treasure
Brother Pleasant Goat Why isn't Sister Nuan Goat?
Because I hadn't come here to study then
Then create another recollection of ours
I want to paint!
Let's take a picture together!
Painted
This is our best treasure