I'll tell you not to
Keep up and don't go away!
Rest assured
I'll leave
I will also go to the tree on the mountain to meet everyone!
What are we going to frick there?
There will be a meteor shower tonight. Let's go there to watch the meteor shower!
A meteor is a stone! I've seen it many times
But there is no meteor shower
There is also a new friend waiting for you!
New friend!
Then let's go quickly!
ah! My fruit...
You're really
You don't want to leave!
Miss it?
Where are the Pleasant Goat Brothers?
Dad, mom!
Where are you?
If you don't bring so much, you just don't listen!
Where is the Bingbing Sheep?
Small gray
Bingbing sheep?
- Have you seen Bingbing Sheep?
Xiao Huihui didn't see it anymore?
This is how things are...
Red We're out to watch the meteor shower
Why bring...so much stuff?
There is nothing on the mountain
All can be used!
Fast, mom!
I think... I saw new friends sooner!
I haven't seen a son so excited for a long time
you do not say
Xiao Huihui Slowly!
Where is Xiao Huihui?
We went back to find it right away
But I didn't find it...
Bingbing Sheep doesn't see it anymore
Then let’s go find it together!
Dad, mom! Where are you?
Who are you? Why cry here?
My name is Xiao Huihui
My name is Bingbingyang!
Originally, my dad and mom and I were going to go to the mountain to watch the meteor shower
But I've gone...
Me too! My brothers and sisters have also left
You should have gone
But what should we do?
Don't worry
I'll leave
I will also go to the tree on the mountain to meet everyone!
Let's go find them together
no!
Dad said that the child had to wait in place when he left...
Leave!
It's very dangerous to run!
Bingbing Sheep, let's not run away...
Maybe there are monsters here too...
Look!
What is this?
This is a dandelion
Just blow it lightly
They'll fly
Flying away!
So beautiful!
There are birds
Wait for me Bingbing Sheep!
Fortunately, I secretly heard about Big Big Wolf and Pleasant Goat
They're going to see the meteor shower
What's so good about a bunch of stones in the universe?
If it weren't for catching the ice sheep, I wouldn't have come
But it's so big here, how can I find it...
It's Bingbing Sheep! How could he be here! ?
It's indeed Bingbing Sheep
And they are not here!
I think they are probably lost
You can change a cannon quickly! I'll catch her!
Just two small things
There is no need to use such powerful weapons
It's too big
There is some truth...
Brother Xiao Huihui, what are you doing?
I'm leaving a record for my dad and mom
They can find us with the logs
I want it too!
Painted!
Look! This is me! This is you!
If I catch the sheep first
You can threaten the king and make me the king!
What are you laughing at?
The king sees me!
Xiao Huang is indeed loyal and has enough ability!
I still have to take it myself!
Get up quickly! They are going far away!
I'll pick it for you!
My little fisherman comes on the hook
It seems that something was hit?
Fun! I want to play, too!
not good! The bee hit! Run!
What's going on? Where is the lamb?
I can't stand it anymore I'm going to catch you now.
Mud Monster Ball!
It is a record number made by Xiao Huihui!
This must be painted by Bingbing Sheep!
Could they have encountered any danger?
If only dad was there!
It's a shooting star!
Dad said it's okay!
I want to let my dad fly over to protect us!
That's the stone!
You're still young, you don't understand
My dad is very bad
Will definitely fly over to protect us!
My dad is also very bad and he will fly too!
My dad will invent it!
My dad will catch bad eggs!
My dad will do a trap!
My dad will do it if your dad is
I thought of it!
I can use the traps my dad taught me to do
Come and deal with monsters!
What is a trap?
Come! I'll teach you
OK!
Found you!
You must catch this time!
There is a sound there
It’s a trap made by Xiao Huihui!
Then
On the other side!
How did we get through?
There is a way
Big Big Wolf Beware
It's my dad!
Bingbing sheep!
My wish has come true!
My dad really flew over to save us!
And we are!
Change quickly!
Scented and burned…
Find someone to control it
Big Big Wolf
These bees again! It's the bee again!
Bingbing sheep! You're fine, right?
You can't run away in the future
OK I'll be in trouble in the future
Xiao Huihui, too
I won't be allowed to run away in the future
good
Small gray
She is the new friend that dad told you before!
It turns out that Bingbing Sheep is the little sheep who is looking for her brother!
He is your new friend!
It turns out that Brother Xiao Huihui is my new friend
Great I have new friends!
Wow! So beautiful!
Bingbing sheep!
Happy wish!
It will really happen!
I hope I will find my brother soon!
I hope Bingbing Sheep will find her brother soon!
My wish will come true soon!
My wishes are definitely ahead of yours!
I'll do it first!
Mine first!