what! Have you not bought a baby?
What is a glutinous baby?
Powder is a delicious food
Have you ever booked Weslie Brother?
Me...
Dad, mom!
Look at the bag I pack
Wow! It's very packaged!
Look, you make you look like a little flower cat!
mother
dad
Then you are the cat father and cat mother
Meow~ Meow~
Meow ~
Of course
Then I want to cover it too!
good
I'll teach you how to make a baby
First of all, you need to have noodles...
Then knead the noodles...
Also prepare the baby
Roll the rind...
Bringing a baby...
Bingbing Yang Is this one you made... a pig?
This is not a pig
It's Brother Weslie, you
Weslie!
We're here to eat the food!
You are here!
These are all wrapped in Bingbing Yang!
Let me taste it first!
No!
It's my first one. I should eat it first
No! I'll eat first!
I'll eat first!
You're all in the back
This is my Bingbing Yang and I will definitely give it to you first!
no! I'll eat first!
I'll eat first! I'll first!
It's so hard to eat
OK, you can eat Weslie first!
I love eating it the most
The Sparky comes first, you can eat it first
Or you eat first!
Too polite!
You eat first
You eat
Weslie Brother! Don't you taste it?
I want to give it to you the most!
How? Is it delicious?
Very good! All of these are for you!
Yes, I remember there is something to do
Weslie Brother! Your baby!
Weslie Brother!
Let's eat the porridge first before leaving
Otherwise, wait a moment
Where did your brother go?
Brother Weslie, you are here!
Weslie Brother!
Why don't you see it again
Where did Weslie goat goat goat goat goat goat go
Weslie
Wolffy?
Are you here?
That... I...
Just go to my house for a meal
That's not very good
Don't be polite and leave
Where has Weslie Brother?
If Weslie eats all the food
May have diarrhea
But Weslie doesn't show up for a day
Bingbing Yang will wait...
How about we sacrificed a little to help them?
You don't want to eat those ingredients, are you?
This is like this
That's it...
Bingbing Yang
These are my snacks!
Is it good to exchange a baby with you?
No, these croquettes are left for Brother Weslie!
So, can I use these toys to exchange with you?
Change?
No problem!
Bingbing Yang
It's okay?
Nothing is OK
It's okay for Huozi
It seems that Weslie will not be finished
Bingbing Yang will not be resting
Weslie Brother
Let’s eat the food!
Are you eating glutinous rice today?
Yes, I have all made them!
tasty!
Really delicious
Very good
Then I'll do it again!
Where is this delicious
Wilie is so good that she can wrap her baby in the first time
In order not to destroy his passion, we all told him... It's delicious
Of course
We should give him more advice, too
Only then will he make progress!
That's it...
It's done!
You taste it!
This time it was even better than the one just now! !
Dad thinks the croquette you made is so delicious!
If the taste was lighter, it would be great
OK! Then I'll give my dad one!
OK! Wilie is so well-behaved
This is the one I've made of you
Dad thinks Weslie bag
It's really delicious!
Mom also likes Weslie bags!
Then I will pack all the cows for you to eat in the future!
The first time I packed the pills are actually not delicious.
But dad and mom will say it tastes good
That's why I have the confidence to continue
But Bingbing Yang's father and mother are not here
My brother can't find it...
If I didn't encourage her...
Wolffy! Thank you for your hospitality!
How about to eat Weslie?
This time you must catch Bingbing Yang and come out
It smells so good, king!
What are they eating?
It seems like you are eating something called "花"
Master, let's have some to eat too!
Dad, I'll give you the last one
All finished eating?
We didn't go to eat the pills, we went to catch the pills.
No, I went to catch Bingbing Yang
Bingbing Yang is right in front
Why hasn't Weslie come back yet?
Bingbing Yang...
Brother Weslie, you are back after finishing your work!
I'll come back to eat your baby
Hutchison...
We are not here to eat the prawns!
We are here to catch Bingbing Yang!
Bingbing Yang!
Captured
King, aren’t we here to catch Bingbing Yang?
Bingbing Yang, you're fine!
Where is my brother's baby?
Bacteria king!
This croquette looks delicious
This purple is for Brother Weslie!
Give it to me quickly!
He actually delivered it to the door by himself
Bingbing Yang!
-Bingbing Yang!!
Chase quickly!
The Paddi use our latest research must-have skills!
Combination!
It won't let you succeed!
Take me a punch
Xiao Huang!
Let you see----my bad!!
Paddi! ! Sparky! !
We're fine
It's time to get a baby
My baby...
Only after eating the pill can I catch Bingbing Yang with strength
It's so hard to eat! ! !
I didn't expect that the pony is used to deal with us
It's fine
They just said my food is not delicious..
actually…
It's really hard to eat!
The unrelated Bingbing Yang
My brother's first time packing of food is not delicious either
Really?
Let's wrap it again!
It will definitely be delicious
Come and taste the repack we have!
Don't worry! It won't be hard to eat this time!
That's right!
Taste it!!
Then let’s taste it!
Very delicious!
Very good!
Brother Weslie, you can taste it too!
It's really delicious!
Leave some for us!
That's mine
You've eaten too much