Doll friend
Very burning...
Who?
Who is it!
Is it difficult to say it is bacteria?
My brother Weslie and I are playing hide-and-seek
Don't tell him I'm here
Is BB Goat here?
BB Goat is not here!
Really not here?
Not here! Not here!
Found you! BB Goat
So you are here
I thought you didn't see it anymore!
Duoduo
This is the bear baby I hold every night when I sleep
Great, finally found you
For a little story, my life was almost gone
Mom, hurry up, I want my first game
Wolffy is not at home. I'm the decision of this home!
The king...
who?
I thought it was Wolffy
Yesterday you went to monitor BB Goat
Let's talk about the situation
Yesterday... was the most painful day in my life...
Very burning!
The lamb is always on BB Goat
No chance to get close to her
Red always forgets to take something
who?
It's the wind blowing
They must be secretly stating something
Listen to it
Right
Yesterday BB Goat found a doll
Is she loves her?
…There is!
I can hide in the doll
Find opportunities to get BB Goat's fingers to unblock
I have to tell the lambs and they
It turns out it was you!
This is a flower
So beautiful
Some creatures especially like to eat flower
There was a bear now...he was careless
Duoduo, wait for me
Hiding in the doll Find a chance to unseal
Weslie Brother
Let's play every home together
I'm busy, let's play with Duoduo first
All right
It would be great if Duoduo moved
Duoduo
Oops
Weslie Brother, I’m moving too much!
Look! Look!
Duoduo
Why don't you move anymore?
Maybe it's dazzled
happiness…
No! !
I'm sent by the moon to play with you
Don't tell anyone else the secret of my movement
Otherwise I will sleep forever
I don't want you to sleep
No doubt, the boss wants me to keep an eye on you!
My boss...
It's useless for you to cry
I cried because of you
I? !
You are obviously worse than that bacteria king
But why do you have to be second?
I can't tell you've come from the bottom of your heart
Of course... not
King!
What are you calling me?
King! Let's go out together to catch BB Goat
Prove that you are the real king!
I've been waiting for a long time today!
We're out! !
etc.
Are you and the lamb friends?
Let me out! ! !
Dare to defeat this king!
I won't play with you anymore
I have to inform the lamb to go
Don't leave! Let me out
Let me out! Let me out...
Wolffy, you dare to bully me! ! !
You not only cheated me, but also humiliated me!
I won't teach you well! Where can I put this face?
Don't move
You have to find a way to get the handprint
Completed!
I only painted my face
I want to play again!
marvelous!
Yes, can you also draw something on my belly?
OK
My power! ! !
BB Goat!
Why are there materials on the ground?
Just a little bit short! ! !
The dolls are dirty, I'll help you clean them
But…
Help! ! !
Duoduo, you're here
Weslie Brother is not here
We can
Let's go out together
Weslie is finally gone I can't bear it anymore!
Take the snail and run!
Where to go? !
snort! I won't play with you
Stay
Help
Duoduo, why are you going to heaven
I'll save you Duoduo
You can collect the line quickly
what
Duoduo
Wait for me!
Finally stopped
I'm here to save you!
what? what?
Duoduo, grab my hand!
not good! If BB Goat fell
What the lambs hear will be troublesome!
I!
Only!
Leave me alone! !
Duoduo, you saved me! ! !
You're fine, right?
I...
I used up all my energy when I just saved you
Then what can I help you?
You put your hands on my belly
It will help me replenish energy
Is that true?
Is it good?
It's much better. Please give it a little more
Weslie!
Wolffy! He actually dared to laugh at me as second place!
Run so fast? !
You give me a stand! Don't run!
Don't run!
Look at my trauma
Blow up!
Start countdown
ten
Nine
eight
Don't be afraid, there are seven seconds
seven
two
Why did it suddenly speed up!
one
Help!
I'm not second!
You're fine
I'm fine, but BB Goat is in danger
The bacteria are hiding in BB Goat's baby and planning to catch her
It's hard for BB Goat to say that the doll will move
Let's go find BB Goat!
Is the energy full?
It's a little bit different
-I will be able to get my strength back soon
A goat? Don't be afraid, one to one can still be a calculation
what? The lambs came all at this time! ?
Even Wolffy is there? Where did the morphine go?
Can't be caught!
Don't try to escape!
Miss it!
Many!
Duoduo Why did you run away
Where have you gone?
He's right in front, let's chase
Fortunately, I escaped from the doll
stop!
Very tired
Bacteria King
You can't escape
What to do
King, I'll help
Let me show you our harm!
Be careful, everyone!
After the morphotrophs are cured
You know it's a disaster!
Duoduo, why don't you talk anymore
Duoduo, is the energy still not enough? You wake up quickly!
Duoduo
Duoduo... must have gone back
My sister also knows Duoduo’s secrets?
Duoduo's mission is to play with BB Goat
He went back after the mission was completed
As long as you keep loving him
He will definitely come and play with you in the future
Duoduo, you need to come back soon
BB Goat Let's go to every house together
OK OK OK!