Still no trace of Brother BB Goat
BB Goat is going to be disappointed again this time
I have a way!
As long as we satisfy some of the hearts of BB Goat
Then she will definitely be very happy
That's right, I have any candy she likes
I can accompany her to read various stories
I can help her make many beautiful clothes
I can go up and down the sea for BB Goat
BB Goat is just a little girl
I want to find the sun!
ah?
I want to know what the sun is doing after going down the mountain
Is there anything else...
It's easier to realize...
Isn’t it said that any wish can be realized?
Of course it's OK!
real
Very good!
What should we do?
And the sun is coming down the mountain
How to find it?
Have it!
Are you looking for the sun?
Are you looking for the sun? hey-hey
Wouldn't you knock on the door first? What are you rushing to do!
King!
BB Goat is looking for the sun
I can become the sun to attract her attention
Then I will take the opportunity to catch the goat!
This is a good idea, change quickly!
The sun is rounded...
Where did I put my football?
It turns out here
Look at my powerful shooting door!
it hurts!
The sun is shining, shining, shining...
Where are the lamps placed?
You can change the lights here
This light bubble is very strange
Why do I always concentrate when I
You can shine!
You just need to become a shape
Let's catch the goat
Anyway, I can't see BB Goat
We'll create a sun down the mountain
Just have a story
Good job!
After the sun goes down the mountain, it will become a light on the top of the fish.
Light up the seabed
Come and see it, this is the light fish exhibition!
The Sun is here!
The sun was eaten by fish!
I made a mistake. This is the small light bubble brought by the light fish.
Not the Sun
So what was the sun doing after going down the mountain?
The sun will become a gift after it goes down the mountain
Gifts to the children in the fourth place
It turns out that the Sun is going to give gifts!
The gift of the old man will meet you tomorrow
Everyone must go and have a look when you have time
This is not a gift old man!
This is the certificate of the gift father-in-law
It's true
You cheat me!
We've been so tired that we've been tying our mouths
What should I do?
I have a way!
You wait for me!
BB Goat Let's go to the underground to find the sun
Is the Sun really here?
The sun has been tired for a day and no electricity
After going down the mountain, you must hide in the cave to charge your electricity
Weslie What did you think of?
I buried a toy sun inside
Just dig according to the map I've painted and you'll find it
I dug up the sun!
Toy sun is here?
What BB Goat dug up was...
I may not be able to find my sunshine today...
It won't
Today I will definitely help you find the Sun
real?
I'll promise you
Thank you, Brother Weslie!
Let's go up the mountain
Weslie
Have you thought of a way out?
right
What is the method of Weslie?
We hold BB Goat
Then find someone to dress up as the sun
Sparky
You can find out
Decorate with a flashlight. It's best to dress up as a sun
Good job!
I'll go right away
BB Goat is there!
Then you will become the sun and go out to attract her!
OK!
Where has Brother Sparky go?
- Upper floor!
- Forgot to remember and spend it!
I'm tired...
BB Goat
I'll take you to find Apple to eat
good!
I'll accompany you!
Next
Just wait for the Sparky
BB Goat, the sun is here
Sparky is so fast
Very realistic sunshine
No doubt about Xiao Huang
What are the Sparky?
etc!
Where is BB Goat! ?
BB Goat and the others went to find something to eat
Come back later
How did he know what I was thinking
The sun is here!
You are the Sparky...
So where is this sun?
I……
It seems that the mistakes are not going to be able to continue
That's right
It was what I sent!
What do you want?
Just want to find BB Goat to unseal
Since she is not here...
Then I'll deal with you first!
Think beautifully
The King
Attack them now!
It's so dazzling. I can't see anything at all
Haven't you prepared the sun lens?
Forgot to close the third eye
I'll give you some
I won't hand it over to you!
Let's split it up!
What to do?
We will be blinded by the strong light when we go together.
Don't do tampering!
We're on!
He actually dared to steal me and flash him!
yes!
I know my strength is hurt
The king attacks them now...
Where is my ink lens?
It's useless no matter how many times you use it!
What a burning moment when did you take away the ink lens!
Duoyan goat sucked the sun lens to me
Winning!
It's the sun!
It turns out that after the sun went down the mountain, she was sleeping in the forest
Yeah yeah
Are you still standing and doing? Go away quickly
The sun is tired after being bright for a day
Let's let it sleep well and don't slap it anymore