Fun
This is too dangerous!
What if I accidentally hit Bingbing Yang?
No more fun!
I know, the village chief…
Bingbing Yang, keep up!
Brother Sparky, wait for me!
Such a skateboard is too dangerous!
Be sure to wear protective equipment to avoid injury
OK, please continue to slip
I happened to bring milk!
Just heat it up and you can drink it!
Bingbing Yang, please wait for a moment
This familiar footsteps... It's hard to tell...
This is too dangerous!
Milk cannot be heated at high temperature
In addition, heating of plastic bags will release toxic gases
Village Chief
Your pussy is too small!
Then what else can we do...
Welcome to the ocean of knowledge!
I'm the most concerned about reading books...
This comic book is so interesting...
The Valley of Ethiopia
It is the exploratory land that countless explorers desire to conquer!
And from ancient times to the present
There is only one warrior from the green grassland
Conquer the Valley of Ethiopia!
My life should not be so ordinary!
I'm going to the Valley of Ethiopia too!
My life shouldn't be so ordinary, either...
You're already extraordinary
So you read the book here
Report First Leader The tent that was exposed to the camp has been set up!
You have a good rest!
Done well
Keep working hard
From now on
The Bacteria Army has only one leader
It's me!
What are you laughing at?
What's going on
I just thought about it
In the past, we explored the happy times of the business together...
Isn't you just want to show off your business?
First leader will satisfy you!
Thank you, head...
This is...
camping?
Eat outside and blow the cool air...
Isn't this comfortable life in the business of slimming?
But...but...
This kind of exposure is not exciting at all!
Stimulate?
have!
Wolffy!
who?
Who?
What's going on
It's you two more!
Don't run!
I just finished swiping!
How? Is it irritating?
It's over yet...
You stand for me!
Who is the mystery of the exploration of the green grassland?
As long as he teaches me a little experience
I can definitely pass through the Valley of Era...
- Lift your head and lift your chest
- The legendary figure...
The feet must stand firm!
No matter how difficult it is, keep smiling!
Hold on!
Brother Tai must be that legendary figure!
Lizard!
Brother Tai!
Even lizards are afraid and they will definitely not dare to rush into the quagmire...
Bao Gongda is so powerful, it must be him!
A snake...
The gang is afraid, how can you get into the giant python forest...
The village chief is definitely not that legendary figure...
never mind
Even if no one leads me, I can pass through the Valley of Erosity!
The head of the wild camp has been set up
You have a good rest!
You said it well
Only in the wild can I feel like I am exposed!
Yes
Come with me quickly!
What's going on? ? !
Click on the book to record
The Valley of Era should be nearby...
Who is it?
I'm a small tree
Bingbing Yang What are you doing here
I'm going to explore, too
We are man-eating flowers
Bacteria king!
Don't run!
Bingbing Yang, let's go
- Hand over Bingbing Yang!
Brother Banana, who will change things, is here!
I'm not a banana!
You can't escape!
Xiao Huang
yes!
Don't run!
stop! Don't run!
Hand me the little one!
Don't even think about it!
This... is this swampy land? ?
So dirty! Help!
Oh no, we're sinking
Help
Sparky  catches it!
Village Chief!
You actually ran to the Valley of Evil
Fortunately, I saw that book followed
Sorry, village chief
etc!
Village chief, are you saying here? ? It is the valley of misfortune!
Yes
And the entrance closed after I came in
So we can only move forward
But there is a marshmallow in front of it
How did we get through?
Don't just look at the front
Pay more attention to the surroundings, look at the above
vine
Come with me
Why are you so fast?
I've been punching the selves every day
Save us!
Xiao Huang, change your ability quickly...
I've escaped from the cave!
There is a pool in front...
Sparky , stop quickly!
So many fish! Let me fly them!
no
Nothing can be hindered
You go and collect some branches and come
Use branches to distract them first
That's now!
Jump!
Village Chief, you are so smart!
Let's go out first
You stand for me! No way to run!
Boss
Help
The exit is right in front!
Be careful
What a big snail!
Sparky? ?
Don't worry, I'm fine!
However, this family has great body shape and strength
Look at the tricks...!
what!
not good!
Careless!
Body moves quickly! Move!
Move!
- Village Chief?
It's nothing more...
It's mine!
Feel less trouble!
Let's have another shot
I will definitely catch you!
Yes, the king
We finally came out!
Village Chief! Bingbing Yang!
Unexpectedly, I also passed the Valley of Era...
And me, and me, and me!
The village chief…I have visited you more this time
Why are you so darn?
You just need to read more books and learn enough knowledge
Can be the same as me
The village chief asked us to read books before, but it turned out that it had a deep meaning...
Difficult to tell
Village Chief, you are the only one
Who knows?
Will my answer be a little bit like this?